<components>
	<component label="Button" className="gfx.controls.Button" states="up|over|down|release|out|disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for Button.

----------------	
Button States                                                           
----------------                                                      
up - Appears when the Button is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
over - Appears when the Button is not selected and the mouse is over the component.
down - Appears when mouse is down over the Button.
release - Appears when the Button has been released.
out - Appears when mouse is out the Button.
disabled - Appears when Button enabled property is set to false.

----------------                                                           
Required Items                                                             
----------------                                                       
textField:TextField                                                 
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the Button.label property 
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="CheckBox" className="gfx.controls.CheckBox" states="up|over|down|release|out|disabled|selected_up|selected_over|selected_down|selected_release|selected_out|selected_disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for CheckBox.

----------------                                                          
CheckBox States                                                           
----------------                                                         
up - Appears when the CheckBox is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
over - Appears when the CheckBox is not selected and the mouse is over the component.
down - Appears when mouse is down over the CheckBox.
release - Appears when the Button has been released.
out - Appears when mouse is out the CheckBox.
disabled - Appears when CheckBox enabled property is set to false.
selected_up - Appears when a CheckBox is selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_over - Appears when CheckBox is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_down - Appears when CheckBox is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_out - Appears when CheckBox is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_disabled - Appears when a CheckBox is selected and disabled.

----------------                                                          
Required Items                                                             
----------------                                                          
textField:TextField                                                        
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the CheckBox.label property
Icon:Graphic 
A graphic indicator for the selection ex: a checkmark graphic
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="DropdownMenu" className="gfx.controls.DropdownMenu" states="up|over|down|release|out|disabled|selected_up|selected_over|selected_down|selected_release|selected_out|selected_disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for DropdownMenu.

----------------      
DropdownMenu States is a compsite component (it requires additional components to work) 
----------------                                                          
up - Appears when the DropdownMenu is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
over - Appears when the DropdownMenu is not selected and the mouse is over the component.
down - Appears when mouse is down over the ComboBox.
release - Appears when the Button has been released.
out - Appears when mouse is out the ComboBox.
disabled - Appears when DropdownMenu enabled property is set to false.
selected_up - Appears when a DropdownMenu is selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_over - Appears when DropdownMenu is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_down - Appears when button is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_out - Appears when button is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_disabled - Appears when a DropdownMenu is selected and disabled.

----------------                                                           
Required Items                                                            
----------------                                                           
textField:TextField                                                        
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the label property from ItemRenderer
A graphic indicator for the selection ex: a checkmark graphic                           
**** Must have inside library components with Linkages for ScrollingList| ListItemRenderer| ScrollBar
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="Label" className="gfx.controls.Label" states="default|disabled|enabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for Label.

----------------                                                          
Label States                                                            	 
----------------                                                           
default - Appears when the Label is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
disabled - Appears when Label is set to enabled.
enabled - Appears when a Label is set to disabled.

----------------                                                           
Required Items                                                             
----------------                                                           
textField:TextField                                                        
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the Button.label property
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="List" className="gfx.controls.ScrollingList" states="default|focused|disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for ScrollingList.

----------------                                                          
ScrollingList States is a compsite component (it requires additional components to work)     	 
----------------                                                           
default - Appears when the ScrollingList is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
focused - Appears when ScrollingList is focused.
disabled - Appears when ScrollingList is set to enabled.

----------------                                                          
Required Items                                                             
----------------                                                           
textField:TextField                                                        
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the Button.label property
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="List Renderer" className="gfx.controls.ListItemRenderer" states="up|over|down|release|out|disabled|selected_up|selected_over|selected_down|selected_release|selected_out|selected_disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for ListItemRenderer.

----------------                                                          
ListItemRenderer States                                                            
----------------                                                        
up - Appears when the ListItemRenderer is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
over - Appears when the ListItemRenderer is not selected and the mouse is over the component.
down - Appears when mouse is down over the ListItemRenderer.
release - Appears when the Button has been released.
out - Appears when mouse is out the ListItemRenderer.
disabled - Appears when ListItemRenderer enabled property is set to false.
selected_up - Appears when a ListItemRenderer is selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_over - Appears when ListItemRenderer is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_down - Appears when ListItemRenderer is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_out - Appears when ListItemRenderer is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_disabled - Appears when a ListItemRenderer is selected and disabled.

----------------                                                          
Required Items                                                             
----------------                                                          
textField:TextField                                                        
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the Button.label property
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="OptionStepper" className="gfx.controls.OptionStepper" states="default|focused|disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for OptionStepper.

----------------                                                          
OptionStepper States is a compsite component (it requires additional **components to work)  
----------------                                                           
default - Appears when the ScrollingList is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
focused - Appears when ScrollingList is focused.
disabled - Appears when ScrollingList is set to enabled.

----------------                                                          
Required Items                                                            
----------------                                                           
textField:TextField                                                       
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the Button.label property
**Button Component Linkage
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="RadioButton" className="gfx.controls.RadioButton" states="up|over|down|release|out|disabled|selected_up|selected_over|selected_down|selected_release|selected_out|selected_disabled" >
		<instructions>	
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for RadioButton.

----------------                                                          
RadioButton States                                                           
----------------                                                          
up - Appears when the RadioButton is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
over - Appears when the RadioButton is not selected and the mouse is over the component.
down - Appears when mouse is down over the RadioButton.
release - Appears when the Button has been released.
out - Appears when mouse is out the RadioButton.
disabled - Appears when RadioButton enabled property is set to false.
selected_up - Appears when a RadioButton is selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_over - Appears when RadioButton is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_down - Appears when RadioButton is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_out - Appears when RadioButton is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
selected_disabled - Appears when a RadioButton is selected and disabled.

----------------                                                           
Required Items                                                             
----------------                                                           
textField:TextField                                                       
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the Button.label property
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="Slider" className="gfx.controls.Slider" states="default|focused|disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for Slider.

----------------                                                           
Slider States is a compsite component (it requires additional components to work) 
----------------
default - Appears when the Slider is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
focused - Appears when Slider is focused.
disabled - Appears when Slider is set to disabled.

----------------                                                           
Required Items                                                            
----------------                                                           
thumb:Button 
(gfx.controls.Button)
track to control sliding 
track:Button 
(gfx.controls.Button)
track to control sliding
**Button Component Linkage 
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="TextArea" className="gfx.controls.TextArea" states="default|focused|disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for TextArea.

----------------                                                           
TextArea States is a compsite component (it requires additional components to work)  
----------------                                                           
default - Appears when the TextArea is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
focused - Appears when TextArea is focused.
disabled - Appears when TextArea is set to disabled.

----------------                                                           
Required Items                                                            
----------------                                                           
textField:TextField                                                       
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the Button.label property
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="TextInput" className="gfx.controls.TextInput" states="default|focused|disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for TextInput.

----------------                                                           
TextInput States                                                           
----------------                                                           
default - Appears when the TextInput is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
focused - Appears when TextInput is focused.
disabled - Appears when TextInput is set to enabled.

----------------                                                           
Required Items                                                             
----------------                                                          
textField:TextField                                                        
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the Button.label property
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="TileList" className="gfx.controls.TileList" states="default|focused|disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for TileList.

----------------                                                           
TileList States  is a compsite component (it requires additional components to work)    
----------------                                                           
default - Appears when the TileList is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
focused - Appears when TileList is focused.
disabled - Appears when TileList is set to enabled.

----------------                                                           
Required Items                                                             
----------------                                                           
textField:TextField                                                        
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the Button.label property|
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
	<component label="ViewStack" className="gfx.controls.ViewStack" states="default|focused|disabled">
		<instructions>
			<![CDATA[ 
Instructions for ViewStack.

----------------                                                           
ViewStack States                                                            
----------------                                                           
default - Appears when the ViewStack is not selected and the mouse is not over the component.
focused - Appears when ViewStack is focused.
disabled - Appears when ViewStack is set to enabled.

----------------                                                           
Required Items                                                             
----------------                                                           
textField:TextField                                                        
A dynamic textfield with the instance name 'textField' displays the Button.label property
			]]>
		</instructions>
	</component>
</components>